Guide to the Charles Hamm Recordings, 1857-1999 HAMM.2005
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Recordings on LP, 1
  - Popular, 1871-1999; IX.
    - Bonnie Koloc, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0191)
      This album includes Newport, Aug. 14 -- Charmer -- Sunday morning movies -- Wind on the water -- On the road -- Mama's blues -- Kentucky dream -- Roll away the grey -- My aunt Edna -- Roslyn.
    - Kris Kristofferson: The Silver-Tongued Devil, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0192)
      This album includes The silver tongued devil and I (4:13) -- Jody and the kid (3:09) -- Billy Dee (2:53) -- Good Christian soldier / B. Bare-B.J. Shaver (3:18) -- Breakdown (a long way from home) (2:41) -- Loving her was easier (than anything I'll ever do again) (3:35) -- The taker / K. Kristofferson-S. Silverstien (3:11) -- When I loved her (2:56) -- The pilgrim - Chapter 33 (3:05) -- Epitaph (black and blue) / K. Kristofferson-D. Fritts (3:21).
    - Cleo Laine: Born on a Friday, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0193)
      This album includes Come back to me / Lerner-Lane (2:53) --Colours ran / Runswick-Crabbe (3:15) --Sunday / Williams-Ascher (2:55) --Do you really want him / Laine-Dankworth (3:00) --Birdsong = Sambalaya / Dankworth (2:49) --Let me be the one / Williams-Nichols (3:17) --Living is easy / Preskett (2:48) --I think it's gonna rain today / Newman (3:22) --Unlucky woman (Born on a Friday) / Feather-Feather (3:30) --Streets of London / McTell (3:57) --Any place I hang my hat is home / Mercer-Arlen (3:56).
    - Led Zeppelin II, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0194)
      This album includes Whole lotta love (5:33) -- What is and what should never be (4:47) -- The lemon song (6:20) -- Thank you (3:50) -- Heartbreaker (4:15) -- Living loving maid (she's just a woman) (2:40) -- Ramble on (4:35) -- Moby Dick (4:25) -- Bring it on home (4:19).
    - Led Zeppelin: Zoso, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0195)
      This album includes Black dog --; Rock and roll --; The battle of evermore --; Stairway to heaven --; Misty mountain hop --; Four sticks --; Going to California --; When the levee breaks.
    - Brenda Lee: 10 Golden Years, 1966, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0196)
      This album includes Jambalaya -- Dynamite -- Bill Bailey, won't you please come home -- Sweet nothin's -- I'm sorry -- Fool #1 -- Dum dum -- All alone am I -- As usual -- Too many rivers.
    - Tom Lehrer: That Was the Year that Was, 1965 (Record HAMM POP 0197)
      This album includes National brotherhood week (2 min., 36 sec.) -- MLF lullaby (2 min., 25 sec.) -- George Murphy (2 min., 10 sec.) -- The folk song army (2 min., 13 sec.) -- Smut (3 min., 15 sec.) -- Send the marines (1 min., 47 sec.) -- Pollution (2 min., 24 sec.) -- Whatever became of Hubert? (2 min., 13 sec.) -- New math (4 min., 31 sec.) -- Alma (5 min., 28 sec.) -- Who's next? (2 min.) -- Wernher von Braun (1 min., 48 sec.) -- The Vatican rag (2 min., 12 sec.).
    - Other Songs by Lieber and Stoller, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0198)
      This album includes Let's bring back world war (3:54) - Longing for a simple time (3:07) - I've got them feelin' too good today blues (2:20) - I ain't here (3:29) - Tango (4:53) - Humphrey bogart (2:33) - I remember (2:28) - Black Denim Trousers and motocycle boots (1:42) - Ready to begin again (3:38) - Is that all there is? (3:46) - Professor Hauptmann's performing dogs (4:39).
    - John Lennon/Plastic Ono Band, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0199)
      This album includes Mother -- Hold on -- I found out -- Working class hero -- Isolation -- Remember -- Love -- Well, well, well -- Look at me -- God -- My mummy's dead.
    - John Lennon Plastic Ono Band: Shaved Fish, 1972, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0200)
      This album includes Give peace a chance; Cold turkey -- Instant karma -- Power to the people -- Mother -- Woman is the nigger of the world -- Imagine -- Whatever gets you thru the night -- Mind games -- #9 dream -- Happy Xmas (war is over); Give peace a chance (reprise).
    - Limo, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0201)
      This album includes Alimony (Ry Cooder) -- Moolah moo mazuma (Sin City Wahh-oo) (Sanford and Townsend) -- Windy City breakdown (Jonathan Cain Band) -- Runaway (Bonnie Raitt) -- Red streamliner (Little Feat) -- Flamingos fly (Van Morrison) -- You make me feel like dancing (Leo Sayer) -- Better than anything (Al Jarreau) -- Walking song (Kate & Anna McGarrigle) -- The runaway (Danny O'Keefe) -- California dreamin' (Eddie Hazel) -- Dreams (Fleetwood Mac) -- Goodbye Miss Sadness (Mylon Le Fevre) -- Didn't wanna hurt cha for another guy (Chunky, Novi & Ernie) -- Nothing but a breeze (Jessie Winchester) -- Living is good (Wendy Waldman) -- Higher & higher (Jesse Colin Young) -- What a way to end it all (Deaf School) -- Aloha ka manini (Gabby Pahinui Hawaiian Band) -- In the mood (Henhouse Five Plus Too) -- Nothin' iz new (Hirth Martinez) -- She (Emmylou Harris) -- Phantom writer (Gary Wright) -- In a stranger's arms (Attitudes) -- Call of the wild (Ted Nugent and the Amboy Dukes) -- You're made that way (Doobie Brothers) -- Tonight's the night (Gonna be alright) (Rod Stewart).
    - The Lovin' Spoonful: Do You Believe in Magic, 1965 (Record HAMM POP 0202)
      This album includes Do you believe in magic -- Blues in the bottle -- Sportin' life -- My gal -- You baby -- Fishin' blues -- Did you ever have to make up your mind -- Wild about my lovin' -- Other side of this life -- Younger girl -- On the road again -- Night owl blues.
    - The Lovin' Spoonful: In Woody Allen's "What's Up, Tiger Lily?", 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0203)
      This album includes Introduction to Flick (2:03) - Pow (Theme from "What's Up, Tiger lily?") (2:28) - Gray Prison Blues (2:150 - Pow Revisited (2:30) - Unconscious Minuet (2:05) - Fishin' Blues (1:58) - Respoken (1:48) - A Cool Milllion (2:20) - Speakin' Of Spoken (2:40) - Lookin' To Spy (2:30) - Phil's Love Theme (2:15) - End Title (4:05).
    - The Very Best Of The Lovin' Spoonful, 1984 (Record HAMM POP 0204)
      This album includes Younger Girl (Sebatian) - Didn't Want To Have To do It (Sebastian) - Daydream (Sebastian) - You Didn't Have To Be So Nice (Sebastian / Boone) - Did You Ever Have To Make Up Your Mind? (Sebastian) - Do You Believe In Magic? (Sebastian) - Summer In The City (Sebastian / Sebastian / Boone) - Rain On The Roof (Sebastian) - Six O'Clock (Sebastian) - Darling Be Home Soon (Sebastian) - Till I Run With You (Gordon / Boone) - Never Going Back (Stewart).
    - Lynyrd Skynyrd: One More From the Road, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0205)
      This album includes Workin' for MCA -- I ain't the one -- Searching -- Tuesday's gone -- Saturday night special -- Travellin' man -- Whiskey rock-a-roller -- Sweet home Alabama -- Gimme three steps -- Call me the breeze -- T for Texas -- The needle and the spoon -- Crossroads -- Free bird.
    - Lynyrd Skynyrd: Street Survivors, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0206)
      This album includes What's your name -- That smell -- One more time -- I know a little -- You got that right -- I never dreamed -- Honky tonk night time man -- Ain't no good life.
    - Parker MacDonell: Home to the Heart, 1983 (Record HAMM POP 0207)
      This album includes I'm headed home / Parker MacDonell, David Sheils (3:32) -- It all comes round / Parker MacDonell, Steve Libbea (3:30) -- Old Ohio / Parker MacDonell, additional music by Chris Petersen (6:00) -- Maggie (4:07); Age old sign (3:54) / Parker MacDonell -- Full in love again / Chris Petersen, Parker MacDonell (3:12) -- The ballad of Wendall Towns (3:38); Bottom line (3:14) / Parker MacDonell, Steve Libbea -- Kristina's lullaby / Parker MacDonell, Severin Browne, Steve Libbea (4:00) -- Home to the heart / Parker MacDonell (4:36).
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra: Between Nothinness & Eternity Live, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0208)
      This album includes Trilogy: The sunlit path; La mere de la mere; Tomorrow's story not the same / J. McLaughlin -- Sister Andrea / J. Hammer -- Dream / J. McLaughlin.
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra: Birds of Fire, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0209)
      This album includes Birds fo Fire - Miles Beyond (Miles Davis) - Celestial Terrestrial Commuters - Sapphire Bullets of Pure Love - Thousand Island Park - Hope - One Word - Sanctuary - Open Country Joy - Resolution.
    - Barry Manilow: Greatest Hits, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0210)
      This album includes Mandy (3:15) -- New York City rhythm (4:42) -- Ready to take a chance again (3:01) -- Looks like we made it (3:33) -- Daybreak (3:36) -- Can't smile without you (3:13) -- It's a miracle (3:42) -- Even now (3:28) -- Bandstand boogie (2:49) -- Tryin' to get the feeling again (3:51) -- Could it be magic (6:50) -- Somewhere in the night (3:26) -- Jump shout boogie (3:03) -- Weekend in New England (3:43) -- All the time (3:15) -- This one's for you (3:25) -- Copacabana (disco) (5:46) -- Beautiful music (4:32) -- I write the songs (3:51).
    - Bob Marley and the Wailers: Uprising, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0211)
      This album includes Coming in from the cold.--Real situation.--Bad card.--We and dem.--Work.--Zion train.--Pimper's paradise.--Could you be loved.--Forever loving jah.--Redemption song.
    - The Marshall tucker Band: Long Hard Ride, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0212)
      This album includes Long hard ride -- Property line -- Am I the kind of man -- Walkin' the streets alone -- Windy City blues -- Holding on to you -- You say you love me -- You don't live forever.
    - McKendree Spring, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0213)
      This album includes I should've known -- I can't make it anymore -- Spock -- What will we do with the child -- Morning glory -- If I gave you everything -- John Wesley Harding -- No regrets -- If the sun should rise.
    - Mary Sol, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0214)
      This album includes Looking for a love (J. Geils Band) -- The noonward race (Mahavishnu Orchestra with John McLaughlin) -- Wang dang doodle (Dr. John) --Why I sing the blues (B.B. King) -- Do you know? (Osibisa) -- Bedroom mazurka (Cactus) -- Ain't wastin' time no more (Allman Brothers Band) -- Take a pebble; Lucky man (Emerson, Lake & Palmer) -- Texas blues; Jelly roll (Nitzinger) -- Sometimes in the morning -- Train of glory (Jonathan Edwards) -- Bring my baby back (John Baldry) -- Respect yourself (Herbie Mann).
    - John McLaughlin: Devotion, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0215)
      This album includes Devotion (11:25) -- Dragon song (4:13) -- Marbles (4:05) -- Siren (5:55) -- Don't let the dragon eat your mother (5:18) -- Purpose of when (4:45).
    - Don McLean: American Pie, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0216)
      This album includes American pie -- Till tomorrow -- Vincent -- Crossroads -- Winterwood -- Empty chairs -- Everybody loves me, baby -- The grave -- Babylon / trad.; arr. by L. Hays, D. McLean.
    - Don McLean: Homeless Brother, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0217)
      This album includes Winter has me in its grip -- La la love you -- Homeless brother -- Sunshine life for me (Sail away Raymond) by G. Harrison -- The legend of Andrew McCrew -- Wonderful baby -- You have lived -- Great big man -- Tangled (like a spider in her hair) -- Crying the the chapel, by A. Glenn -- Did you know.
    - Melanie: Candles in the Rain, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0218)
      This album includes Candles in the rain -- Lay down (candles in the rain) -- Carolina in my mind -- Citiest people -- What have they done to my song -- Alexander beetle -- The good guys -- Lovin baby girl -- Ruby Tuesday -- Leftover wine.
    - Melanie: Gather Me, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0219)
      This album includes Little bit of me -- Some day I'll be a farmer -- Steppin' -- Brand new key -- Ring around the moon -- Ring the living bell; Shine the living light (Chant); Ring the living bell; Shine the living light (Chant reprise) -- Railroad -- Kansas -- Some say (I got devil) -- Center of the circle -- What wondrous love -- Baby day -- Tell me why.
    - The Mills Brothers Greatest Hits, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0220)
      This album includes Paper doll / Black -- You always hurt the one you love / Roberts-Fisher -- Till then / Wood-Seiler-Marcus -- Across the alley from the Alamo / Greene -- Lazy river / Carmichael-Arodin -- The glow-worm / Lincke-Mercer-Robinson -- Nevertheless (I'm in love with you) / Kalmar-Ruby -- Cab driver / Parks -- Be my life's companion / Hilliard-De Lugg -- The Jones boy / Mizzy-Curtis.
    - The Mills Brothers' Great Hits Vol. 2, 1960 (Record HAMM POP 0221)
      This album includes Opus one (1:43) -- You're nobody 'til somebody loves you (2:21) -- Daddy's little girl (2:57) -- Standing on the corner (2:15) -- I don't know enough about you (2:11) -- I love you so much it hurts (2:26) -- Manana (2:05) -- You broke the only heart that ever loved you (2:24) -- The Jones boy (2:18) -- I'm afraid to love you (2:31) -- You never miss the water till the well runs dry (2:40) -- I guess I'll get the papers (and go home) (2:17).
    - Steve Miller Band: Book of Dreams, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0222)
      This album includes Threshold -- Jet airliner -- Winter time -- Swingtown -- True fine love -- Wish upon a star -- Jungle love -- Electro lux imbroglio -- Sacrifice -- The stake -- My own space -- Babes in the wood.
    - Steve Miller Band: Fly Like an Eagle, 1976 (Record HAMM POP 0223)
      This album includes Space intro (1:15) -- Fly like an eagle (4:42) -- Wild mountain honey (4:30) -- Serenade (3:10) -- Dance, dance, dance (2:16) -- Mercury blues (3:43) -- Take the money and run (2:48) -- Rock 'n me (3:05) -- You send me (2:40) -- Blue odyssey (1:00) -- Sweet Maree (4:16) -- The window (4:19).
    - Steve Miller Band: Number 5, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0224)
      This album includes Good morning -- I love you -- Going to the country -- Hot chili -- Tokin's -- Going to Mexico -- Steve Miller's midnight tango -- Industrial military complex hex -- Jackson-Kent blues -- Never kill another man.
    - Steve Miller Band: Rock Love, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0225)
      This album includes The gangster is back -- Blues without blame -- Love shock -- Let me serve you -- Rock love -- Harbor lights -- Deliverance.
    - Chad Mitchell Trio: Singin' Our Mind, 1962 (Record HAMM POP 0226)
      This album includes Dubarry done gone again _2:24) - Ain't no more cane on this brazos (3:02) - Four strong winds (3:34) - Alma mater (2:59) - An Irish song (2:39) - I feel so good about it (2:07) - The marvelous toy (2:46) - Maladiozhenaya (The young ones) (2:28) - Nobody knows you (3:31) - The bonny street of FYVE-10 (3:08) - Willie Seton (2:18) - Twevlve days (5:33).
    - Joni Mitchell, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0227)
      This album includes I came to the city. I had a king; Michael from mountains; Night in the city; Marcie; Nathan La Franeer -- Out of the city and down to the seaside. Sisotowbell Lane; The dawntreader; The pirate of penance; Song to a seagull; Cactus tree.
    - Joni Mitchell: Clouds, 1969 (Record HAMM POP 0228)
      This album includes Tin angel -- Chelsea morning -- I don't know where I stand -- That song about the midway -- Roses blue -- The gallery -- I think I understand -- Songs to aging children come -- The fiddle and the drum -- Both sides, now.
    - Joni Mitchell: For the Roses, 1972 (Record HAMM POP 0229)
      This album includes Banquet -- Cold blue steel and sweet fire -- Barangrill -- Lesson in survival -- Let the wind carry me -- For the roses -- See you sometime -- Electricity -- You turn me on I'm a radio -- Blonde in the bleachers -- Woman of heart and mind -- Judgment of the moon and stars (Ludwig's tune).
    - Joni Mitchell: Ladies of the Canyon, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0230)
      This album includes Morning Morgantown -- For free -- Conversation -- Ladies of the canyon -- Willie -- The arrangement -- Rainy night house -- The priest -- Blue boy -- Big yellow taxi -- Woodstock -- The circle game.
    - The Moody Blues: Days of Future Passed, 1967 (Record HAMM POP 0231)
      This album includes T he day begins.-- Dawn; Dawn is a feeling.--The morning; Another morning.--Lunch break; Peak hour.--The afternoon; Forever afternoon (Tuesday?).--Evening; The sun set; twilight time.--The night; Nights in white satin.
    - Moonrock, 1988 (Record HAMM POP 0232)
      This album includes The Other (Brad Hoopes…4:02) - Lock 'N' Key (Tim Malcolm…3:08) - Soft Life (Benjamin Moynihan…5:31) - Stretchy (John Nason…7:16) - Hard To Find (John Nason…4:52) - Mannequin (Benjamin Moynihan…6:31) - Clouds (Tim Malcolm…6:14) - Quiescence (Brad Hoops…5:23).
    - Van Morrison: Wavelength, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0233)
      This album includes Kingdon Hall (5:59) -- Checkin' it out (3:29) -- Natalia (4:04) -- Venice U.S.A. (6:32) -- Lifetimes (4:15) -- Wavelength (5:44) -- Santa Fe; Beautiful obsession (7:04) -- Hungry for your love (3:45) -- Take it when you find it (8:40).
    - Mothers of Invention: Burnt Weeny Sandwich, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0234)
      This album includes W P L J (the four deuces) -- Igor's boogie, phase one -- Overture to A holiday in Berlin -- Theme from Burnt weeny sandwich -- Igor's boogie, phase two -- Holiday in Berlin, full blown -- Aybe Sea -- Little house I used to live in -- Valarie.
    - Moving Pictures: Days of Innocence, 1982 (Record HAMM POP 00235)
      This album includes Nothing to do -- What about me -- Round again -- Bustin' loose -- Wings -- The angel and the madman -- Sweet Cherie -- So tired -- Joni and the romeo -- Streetheart.
    - Randy Newman: Good Old Boys, 1974 (Record HAMM POP 0236)
      This album includes Rednecks -- Birmingham -- Marie -- Mr. President (have pity on the working man) -- Guilty -- Louisiana 1927 -- Every man a king -- Kingfish -- Wedding in Cherokee County -- Back on my feet again -- Rollin'.
    - Randy Newman: Live, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0237)
      This album includes Mama told me not to come.--Tickle me.--I'll be home.--So long dad.--Living without you.--Last night I had a dream.--I think it's going to rain today.--Lover's prayer.--Maybe I'm doing it wrong.--Yellow man.--Old Kentucky home.--Cowboy.--Davy the fat boy.--Lonely at the top.
    - Randy Newman: 12 Songs, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0238)
      This album includes Have you seen my baby? -- Let's burn down the cornfield -- Mama told me not to come -- Suzanne -- Lover's prayer -- Lucinda -- Underneath the Harlem moon -- Yellow man -- Old Kentucky home -- Rosemary -- If you need oil -- Uncle Bob's midnight blues.
    - Olivia Newton John's Greatest Hits, 1973, 1977 (Record HAMM POP 0239)
      This album includes If not for you / Bob Dylan (2:50) -- Changes / Olivia Newton-John (2:27) -- Let me be there / John Rostill (3:00) -- If you love me (let me know) / John Rostill (3:12) -- I honestly love you / Peter Allen, Jeff Barry (3:36) -- Have you never been mellow / John Farrar (3:28) -- Please Mr. please / Bruce Welch, John Rostill (3:24) -- Something better to do / John Farrar (3:16) -- Let it shine / Linda Hargrove (2:26) -- Come on over / Barry Gibb, Robin Gibb (3:38) -- Don't stop believin' / John Farrar (3:37) -- Sam / John Farrar, Hank Marvin, Don Black (3:41).
    - Nilsson Sings Newman, 1970 (Record HAMM POP 0240)
      This album includes Vine St. -- Love story -- Yellow man -- Caroline -- Cowboy -- The beehive state -- I'll be home -- Living without you -- Dayton, Ohio 1903 -- So long dad.
    - Ted Nugent: Weekend Warriors, 1978 (Record HAMM POP 0241)
      This album includes Need you bad -- One woman -- I got the feelin' -- Tight spots -- Venom soup -- Smokescreen -- Weekend warriors -- Cruisin' -- Good friends and a bottle of wine -- Name your poison.
    - Yoko Ono: Season of Glass, 1981 (Record HAMM POP 0242)
      This album includes Goodbye sadness (3:48) -- Mindweaver (4:24) -- Even when you're far away (4:12) -- Nobody sees me like you do (3:31) -- Turn of the wheel (2:41) -- Dogtown (3:22) -- Silver horse (3:03) -- I don't know why (4:18) -- Extension 33 (2:45) -- No, no, no (2:43) -- Will you touch me (2:37) -- She gets down on her knees (4:13) -- Toyboat (3:31) -- Mother of the universe (4:26).
    - Mike Oldfield: Tubular Bells, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0243)
      This album includes Tubular bells.
    - More of Roy Orbison's Greatest Hits, 1966 (Record HAMM POP 0244)
      This album includes It's over (02:47) -- Blue bayou (02:29) -- Indian wedding (02:59) -- Falling (02:22) -- Working for the man (02:25) -- Pretty paper (02:41) -- Mean woman blues (02:23) -- Lana (02:46) -- In dreams (02:46) -- Leah (02:37) -- Borne on the wind (02:50) -- What'd I say (02:50).
    - The Original Hits, Volume 2 (Record HAMM POP 0245)
      This album includes Stranded in the jungle / The Cadets (3:04) - Come softly to me / The Fleetwoods (2:25) - Short fat fannie / Larry Williams (2:20) - City of angels / The Highlights (2:16) - I'm available / Margie Rayburn (1:50) - Cherry Pie / Marvin & Johnny (2:40) - Summertime blues / Eddie Cochran (1:53) - You're sixteen / Johnny Burnette (1:56) - Perfidia / The Ventures (2:03) - Lovey Dovey / Buddy Knox (2:11) - Forever / The Little Dippers (2:18) - Smokie Part II / Bill Black Combo (2:05) - Rubber Ball / Bobby Vee (2:17).
    - Van Dyke Parks: Song Cycle, 1968 (Record HAMM POP 0246)
      This album includes Vine street (R. Newman -3:38) - Palm desert (Van Dyke ParKs -3:05) - Window's walk (Van Dyke Parks -3:10) - Laurel Canyon Blud. (Van Dyke Parks -:25) - The all goldern (Van Dyke Parks -3:12) - Van Dyke Parks (Public Domain :55) - Public Domain (Van Dyke Parks 2:30) - Donovan's colours (Donovan Leitch 3:39) - The Attic (Van Dyke Parks -3:35) - Laurel Canyon Blvd (Van Dyke Parks -1:17) - By the people (Van Dyke Parks -5:57) - Pot Pourri (Van Dyke Parks -1:07).
    - Pere Ubu: The Art of Walking, 1980 (Record HAMM POP 0247)
      This album includes Go -- Rhapsody in pink -- Arabia -- Tribute to Miles -- Misery goats -- Loop -- Rounder -- Birdies -- Lost in art -- Horses -- Crush this horn.
    - Tom Petty: Full Moon Fever, 1989 (Record HAMM POP 0248)
      This album includes Free fallin' -- I won't back down -- Love is a long road -- A face in the crowd -- Runnin' down a dream -- Feel a whole lot better -- Yer so bad -- Depending on you -- The apartment song -- Alright for now -- A mind with a heart of its own -- Zombie zoo.
    - Pink Floyd: The Dark Side of the Moon, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0249)
      This album includes Speak to me -- Breathe -- On the run --Time -- The great gig in the sky --Money - Us and them -- Any Colour you like -- Brain damage -- Eclipse.
    - The Golden Hits of the Platters, 1973 (Record HAMM POP 0250)
      This album includes I love you 1,000 times.--With this ring.--Washed ashore (on a lonely island in the sea).--The great pretender.--My prayer.--Only you (and you alone).--(You've got) the magic touch.--Harbor lights.--Smoke gets in your eyes.--I'm sorry.--Twilight time.--Heaven on earth.
    - Prince and the Revolution: Purple Rain, 1984 (Record HAMM POP 0251)
      This album includes Let's go crazy (4:39) -- Take me with u (3:54) -- The beautiful ones (5:15) -- Computer blue (3:59) -- Darling Nikki (4:15) -- When doves cry (5:52) -- I would die 4 u (2:51) -- Baby I'm a star (4:20) -- Purple rain (8:45).
    - John Prine, 1971 (Record HAMM POP 0252)
      This album includes Illegal smile -- Spanish pipedream -- Hello in there -- Sam Stone -- Paradise -- Pretty good -- Your flag decal won't get you into heaven anymore -- Far from me -- Angel from Montgomery -- Quiet man -- Donald and Lydia -- Six o'clock news -- Flashback blues.
    - John Prine: Aimless Love, 1984 (Record HAMM POP 0253)
      This album includes Be my friend tonight -- Aimless love -- Me, myself and I -- The oldest baby in the world -- Slow boat to China -- Bottomless lake -- Maureen, Maureen -- Somewhere someone's falling in love -- People puttin' people down -- Unwed fathers -- Only love.
    - John Prine: Common Sense, 1975 (Record HAMM POP 0254)